ity.im 2019-06-26

# ity.im URL Shortener & Ad Network

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ity.im collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://ity.im website ("Site").

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, birthdate, phone number or other pieces of personal information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer or mobile device, device identifiers ("UUID") and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet Protocol ("IP") address, computer or device location information (which may include GPS coordinates), the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

### Analytics information

We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools and services, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our Site. These tools collect information sent by Users' browsers or mobile devices, including the pages visited and other information that assists us in improving the Site.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### Web beacons

When you use the Site, we may employ small files known as web beacons, which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use web beacons in HTML-formatted emails sent to Users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients.

### Information we may receive from third parties

We may receive information about Users from third parties. For example, if a User accesses our Site through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by following,Eliking,Eor linking the User's account to our Site, etc., that third party may pass certain information about the User of its service to us. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with that account (for example, Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that the User has permitted the third party to share with us, and any information the User has made public in connection with that service. If the User allows us access to a friends list, then User's friendsEuser IDs, and User's connection to those friends may be used and stored.

### How we use collected information

ity.im may collect and use Users' personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To run and operate our Site_  
We may need your information to operate, or display content on, the Site correctly. 
  * _To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * _To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * _To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 
  * _To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Electronic newsletters

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

ity.im has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will update the date at the bottom of this document. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

This document was last updated on September 3, 2015
